Guide to the News Service Biographical Files, circa 1930s - 2004
Duke University. University Archives
- Addition, 2004 [A2004-19] (Box 60)
  - Faculty and staff (Box 60)
    - Ware, R. M. (Box 106)
    - Ware, Russell E. (Box 106)
    - Warner, Seth (Box 106)
    - Warren, David G. (Box 106)
    - Warren, James V. (Box 106)
    - Washington, Mary K. (Box 106)
    - Wasiolek, Suzanne (Box 106)
    - Waters, Raymond "Buckey" (Box 106)
    - Waters, William E. (Box 106)
    - Watkins, James Mayer (Box 106)
    - Watkins, W. David (Box 106)
    - Watling, Elizabeth (Box 107)
    - Watson, Cornelia Anne (Box 107)
    - Watson, Karl B. (Box 107)
    - Watson, J. Ray (Box 107)
    - Watson, John B. (Box 107)
    - Watson, Richard L. [History] (Box 107)
    - Watson, Richard L. [History], d. 2000 (Box 107)
    - Watts, David (Box 107)
    - Waugh, Robert Andrew (Box 107)
    - Way, Katherine (Box 107)
    - Weaver, Ben F. (Box 107)
    - Webb, Bailey (Box 107)
    - Webb, Wilfred (Box 107)
    - Webb-Mitchell, Brett (Box 107)
    - Weber, Bruce A. (Box 107)
    - Webster, George D. (Box 107)
    - Weeks, Benjamin F. (Box 107)
    - Wegmann, Helmut (Box 107)
    - Weinberg, Daniel I. (Box 107)
    - Weinberg, Joe Brice (Box 107)
    - Weiner, Richard (Box 107)
    - Weinerth, John Louis (Box 107)
    - Weinhold, Kent J. (Box 107)
    - Weintraub, E. Roy (Box 107)
    - Weisenfeld, Gennifer (Box 107)
    - Weisfeld, Morris (Box 107)
    - Weiss, Jay (Box 107)
    - Weistart, John (Box 107)
    - Weitz, Henry (Box 107)
    - Welch, Donald J. (Box 107)
    - Weldon, Wilson Osbourne [Divinity] (Box 107)
    - Weldon, Wilson Osbourne [Divinity], d. 3/15/1998 (Box 107)
    - Welfling, Weldon (Box 107)
    - Weller, Henry R. [Physics] (Box 107)
    - Weller, Robert (Box 107)
    - Wellman, David K. (Box 107)
    - Wellons, J. D., Jr. (Box 107)
    - Wells, Richard L. (Box 107)
    - Wells, Warner (Box 107)
    - Welther, Frederick L. (Box 107)
    - Wentz, William Robert (Box 107)
    - Werman, David S. (Box 107)
    - Werner, Daniel P. (Box 107)
    - Wertz, Martha L. (Box 107)
    - West, Mike (Box 107)
    - Westerhoff, John H., III [Divinity], 1970s (Box 107)
    - Westerhoff, John H., III [Divinity], 1980s-early 1990s (Box 107)
    - Westman, Eric C. (Box 107)
    - Wetherington, Gerald T. (Box 107)
    - Whalen, Robert (Box 107)
    - Whaley, Robert E. (Box 107)
    - Whanger, Alan D. [Includes Shroud of Turin Photographs] (Box 107)
    - Wharton, Annabel Jane (Box 107)
    - Wharton, George W., Jr. (Box 107)
    - Wharton, John Marcus (Box 107)
    - Wheat, Robert W. (Box 107)
    - White, Frances J. (Box 107)
    - White, Heidi (Box 107)
    - White, Judith (Box 107)
    - White, Newman Ivey (Box 107)
    - White, Richard A. (Box 107)
    - White, Stephen W. (Box 107)
    - Whitefield, Clarence E. (Box 107)
    - Whitener, Fred W. (Box 107)
    - Whiteside, Tom (Box 107)
    - Whitford, William E. (Box 107)
    - Whitridge, Eugenia (Box 107)
    - Whittington, Erma Paden (Box 107)
    - Whorton, A. Richard (Box 107)
    - Widmann, Frances (Box 107)
    - Wiener, Jonathon B. [Pediatric Urology] (Box 107)
    - Wiener, Jonathon B. [Pediatric Urology], 1999 (Box 107)
    - Wigen, Karen (Box 107)
    - Wiggens, Daphne (Box 107)
    - Wilbur, Henry Miles (Box 108)
    - Wilbur, Karl (Box 108)
    - Wilbur, Ralph S. (Box 108)
    - Wilder, Pelham (Box 108)
    - Wilfert, Catherine (Box 108)
    - Wilkins, Robert H. (Box 108)
    - Wilkins, Roland (Box 108)
    - Wilkinson, Alice S. (Box 108)
    - Wilkinson, Howard C. (Box 108)
    - Wilkinson, Steven (Box 108)
    - Wilkinson, William E. (Box 108)
    - Willett, Hilda Pope (Box 108)
    - Williams, Blythe (Box 108)
    - Williams, Brackette (Box 108)
    - Williams, Christina (Box 108)
    - Williams, George Trevor (Box 108)
    - Williams, George Walton (Box 108)
    - Williams, John Wiley [General Internal Medicine] (Box 108)
    - Williams, Kenny J. (Box 108)
    - Williams, Larry W. (Box 108)
    - Williams, Leland H. (Box 108)
    - Williams, Mary Lou (Box 108)
    - Williams, Paul O. (Box 108)
    - Williams, Peter F. (Box 108)
    - Williams, R. Sanders (Box 108)
    - Williams, Redford B. (Box 108)
    - Williams, Robert Sanders "Sandy" [DU Medicine] (Box 108)
    - Williams, Wayne (Box 108)
    - Williamson, Donald S. (Box 108)
    - Willimon, William H. "Will" [Duke Chapel] (Box 108)
    - Willis, Deborah (Box 108)
    - Willis, Susan (Box 108)
    - Willis, William H. [Classical Studies (Greek)] (Box 108)
    - Willis, William H. [Classical Studies (Greek)], d. 7/13/2000 (Box 108)
    - Wills, Jim (Box 108)
    - Willson, A. Leslie (Box 108)
    - Wilson, A. Jack III (Box 108)
    - Wilson, Barry [Football] (Box 108)
    - Wilson, Bob (Box 108)
    - Wilson, Gerald (Box 108)
    - Wilson, James F. (Box 108)
    - Wilson, James Robert (Bob) (Box 108)
    - Wilson, James W. (Box 108)
    - Wilson, Joanne A. P. (Box 108)
    - Wilson, John (Box 108)
    - Wilson, Kenneth [Infectious Diseases] (Box 108)
    - Wilson, Kenneth [Infectious Diseases], 2001 (Box 108)
    - Wilson, Neil L. (Box 108)
    - Wilson, Robert L. (Box 108)
    - Wilson, Robert N. (Box 108)
    - Wilson, Robert R. (Box 108)
    - Wilson, Ruby Leila (Box 108)
    - Wilson, Shirley S. "Red" (Box 108)
    - Wilson, Thomas George (Box 109)
    - Wilson, Wilkie A. (Box 109)
    - Wilson, William (Box 109)
    - Wilson, William H. (Box 109)
    - Winer, Eric [Hematology and Medical Oncology] (Box 109)
    - Winfree, Robert G. (Box 109)
    - Wing, Cliff W., Jr. (Box 109)
    - Winkler, Robert L. (Box 109)
    - Winsborough, Halliman H. (Box 109)
    - Wintermute, Orval Stewart (Box 109)
    - Wisoker, Kenneth A. (Box 109)
    - Witelski, Thomas (Box 109)
    - Withers, Loren (Box 109)
    - Witt, Ronald (Box 109)
    - Wittels, Benjamin (Box 109)
    - Wittig, Ellen W. (Box 109)
    - Wolbarsht, Myron L. (Box 109)
    - Wolf, Edwin (Box 109)
    - Wolf, Patrick [Biomedical Engineering], 1998 (Box 109)
    - Wolfe, Walter G. (Box 109)
    - Wolpert, Robert L. (Box 109)
    - Wolslagel, Earl W. (Box 109)
    - Womble, Hilburn (Box 109)
    - Wong, Kai Tak (Box 109)
    - Wood, Donald J. (Box 109)
    - Wood, James H. (Box 109)
    - Wood, Patricia (Box 109)
    - Wood, Peter (Box 109)
    - Woodbury, Max A. (Box 109)
    - Woods, Frank W. (Box 109)
    - Woods-Powell, C. T. (Box 109)
    - Woody, Robert H. (Box 109)
    - Woodyard, Alma Lorraine (Box 109)
    - Worcester, Barbara (Box 109)
    - Worde, Boyd Thomas (Box 109)
    - Worley, Gordon (Box 109)
    - Wortman, Paul M. (Box 109)
    - Wray, Julia (Box 109)
    - Wright, Don (Box 109)
    - Wright, George Carlton (Box 109)
    - Wright, Linda Colleen (Box 109)
    - Wright, Patricia (Box 109)
    - Wu, Lawrence (Box 109)
    - Wuenscher, James Edward (Box 109)
    - Wyngaarden, James (Box 109)
    - Wynkoop, Rodney Alan (Box 109)
    - Yaggy, Duncan (Box 109)
    - Yancy, William S. (Box 109)
    - Yang, Dennis T. [Economics], 2001 (Box 109)
    - Yang, Weitao (Box 109)
    - Yoder, Barbara A. (Box 109)
    - Yohe, William P. (Box 110)
    - Yoho, James G. (Box 110)
    - York, Brantley (Box 110)
    - Young, Betty Irene (Box 110)
    - Young, Charles R. (Box 110)
    - Young, Franklin W. (Box 110)
    - Young, Helen R. (Box 110)
    - Young, James S. (Box 110)
    - Young, Stephen L. (Box 110)
    - Young, W. Glenn (Box 110)
    - Younger, Ben (Box 110)
    - Younger, John G. (Box 110)
    - Younts, Worth D. (Box 110)
    - Yuan, Fan (Box 110)
    - Zalutsky, Michael Rod (Box 110)
    - Zarkin, Gary (Box 110)
    - Zegler, Richard (Box 110)
    - Zener, Karl E. (Box 110)
    - Zheng, Fangyang (Box 110)
    - Zhou, Xueguang (Box 110)
    - Zinna, Rosario F. (Box 110)
    - Zipkin, Paul H. (Box 110)
    - Zmijewski, Chester M. (Box 110)
    - Zung, William Wen-Kwai (Box 110)
  - Notables (Box 110)
    - Allison, John A. (Box 111)
    - Anlyan, William George [Chancellor; Head, DUMC; Endowment Trustee], 1950s-1990s (Box 111)
    - Applewhite, James W. [English ], 1970s-2000s (Box 111)
    - Bailey, A. Purnell [Alumnus] (Box 111)
    - Barber, James David [Political Science], 1972-1999 (Box 111)
    - Bennett, Floyd S. [Alumnus and Employee], 1950s (Box 111)
    - Best, Michael [Alumnus; Metropolitian Opera] (Box 111)
    - Boomer, Gen. Walter [Alumnus] (Box 111)
    - Brady, Charles E., Jr. (Box 111)
    - Brown Less [Alumnus; Band of Renown] (Box 111)
    - Browne, John C. [Alumnus] (Box 111)
    - Caldwell, John Tyler [Alumnus; Chancellor, NCSU] (Box 111)
    - Campbell, Bill [Alumnus, Law; Mayor, Atlanta] (Box 111)
    - Carroll, Charles F. [Alumnus] (Box 111)
    - Carswell, George Harrold [Alumnus; Judge] (Box 111)
    - Chambers, John [Alumnus; Pres. and CEO Cisco] (Box 112)
    - Chappell, Fred [Alumnus; Poet] (Box 112)
    - Chavis, Benjamin [Alumnus, Divinity School] (Box 112)
    - Creech, Jimmy [Alumnus, Divinity School] (Box 112)
    - Dalton, Harry L. [Alumnus; Dalton Rare Book Room (Perkins Library)], d.1990 (Box 112)
    - Daniels, G. Neil [Alumnus, Law] (Box 112)
    - Darrow, Siobhan [Alumnus] (Box 112)
    - Davis, Brian [Alumnus; Basketball] (Box 112)
    - Davis, Charles S. [Alumnus] (Box 112)
    - Davis, Lynn [Alumna; Member, Carter Administration] (Box 112)
    - DeParle, Jason [Alumnus] (Box 112)
    - Dole, Elizabeth Hanford [Alumna; Senator; Univ. Trustee], 1970s-2000s (Box 112)
    - Duke, Doris [Daughter of J. B. Duke; Trustee], 1920-1979 (Box 112)
    - Earle, Sylvia [Alumna, A.M. ' 56, Ph.D. ' 66] (Box 112)
    - Evans, Harold [Professor] (Box 112)
    - Feinstein, John [Alumnus, T ' 77; Sports Journalist] (Box 112)
    - Felker, Clay [Alumnus, T ' 51; Magazine Publisher] (Box 112)
    - Franklin, John Hope [Professor; Historian; Author; Endowment Trustee], 1980-1999 (Box 112)
    - Galifianakis, Nick [Alumnus; Law; Politician] (Box 112)
    - Gibbons, John [Alumnus (1954 Ph.D., Physics); Federal Office of Energy Conservation; White House Office of Science and Technology Policy] (Box 112)
    - Gish, Annabeth [Alumna; Actress (X-Files)] (Box 112)
    - Goode, David [Alumnus; Chairman, Norfolk Southern] (Box 112)
    - Goodman, Jim [Alumnus; CEO, Capitol Broadcasting Co.] (Box 112)
    - Griffin, Gordon [Alumnus; U.S. Ambassador to Canada] (Box 112)
    - Gulley, Wilbur Paul "Wib" [Alumnus; Mayor, Durham, N.C.] (Box 112)
    - Hanks, Nancy [Alumna; National Endowment for the Arts; Univ. Trustee] (Box 112)
    - Hardin, Paul [Alumnus (T 1952, Law 1954); Former Chancellor, UNC-CH; Univ. Trustee] (Box 112)
    - Harrigan, Steve [Alumnus; Foreign Correspondent, Fox News] (Box 112)
    - Harrington, Milton E. [Alumnus; CEO, Liggett and Myers] (Box 112)
    - Hartman, David [Alumnus; Host, Good Morning America] (Box 112)
    - Hayes, Robin [Alumnus; U.S. Congressman] (Box 112)
    - Hill, Grant [Alumnus; Basketball (All America); Five-time NBA All-Star] (Box 112)
    - Humphreys, Josephine [Alumna; Author] (Box 112)
    - Hunt, Joseph M. (Box 112)
    - Hutson, Harold H. [Alumnus (1935); Pres., Greensboro College ] (Box 112)
    - Hyde, Henry (Box 112)
    - John, Ralph C. [Alumnus (School); Pres., Simpson College ] (Box 113)
    - Jordan, B. Everett [Alumnus; U.S. Senator] (Box 113)
    - Jordan, Henry W. [Alumnus] (Box 113)
    - Jordan, Robert W. [Alumnus; U.S. Ambassador to Saudi Arabia] (Box 113)
    - Kelly, Susan (Box 113)
    - Kilburn, S. Collins [Alumnus; Divinity School] (Box 113)
    - Killian, James Rhyne, Jr. [Alumnus; Pres., MIT] (Box 113)
    - Klayman, Larry [Alumnus] (Box 113)
    - Lader, Philip [Alumnus; U.S. Ambassador to the Court of St. James] (Box 113)
    - Laettner, Christian [Alumnus; Basketball; Blue Devil Ventures (Real Estate Development)] (Box 113)
    - Lagos, Ricardo [Alumnus; Pres. Of Chile] (Box 113)
    - Loomis, Robert D. (Box 113)
    - Mack, John J. [Alumnus; Pres., Morgan Stanley; Univ. Trustee] (Box 113)
    - Matlock, Jack F., Jr. [Alumnus; U.S. Ambassador to the U.S.S.R.] (Box 113)
    - McLarin, Kim [Alumna; Author] (Box 113)
    - Mumford, Lawrence Quincy [Alumnus; 11th Librarian of Congress] (Box 113)
    - Murchison, Clint, Jr. [Alumnus; Financier] (Box 113)
    - Murphy, Charles [Alumnus; Undersecretary of Agriculture] (Box 113)
    - Nixon, Edward Calvert [Alumnus; Younger brother of Richard M. Nixon] (Box 113)
    - Nixon Library [News Clippings] (Box 113)
    - Nixon, Richard Milhous [Alumnus; U.S. President (1969-1974)] (Box 113)
    - Payne, Peggy (Box 113)
    - Peterson, Michael [Alumnus; Author; Convicted of murdering his wife] (Box 113)
    - Reveley, W. Taylor, Jr. [Alumnus; Pres., Hampden Sydney College] (Box 113)
    - Rose, Charlie [Alumnus; Television Journalist; Recipient of Futrell Award] (Box 113)
    - Ruffin, Julian M. [DUMC] (Box 113)
    - Ruffin, William H. (Box 113)
    - Sanford, Terry [President of Duke University] (Box 113)
    - Sanford, Terry [President of Duke University], 1970s (Box 113)
    - Sanford, Terry [President of Duke University], 1980s (Box 113)
    - Sanford, Terry [President of Duke University], 1987- (Box 113)
    - Sanford, Terry [President of Duke University], 1992 (Box 113)
    - Sanford, Terry [President of Duke University], 1993 (Box 113)
    - Sanford, Terry [President of Duke University], 1994 (Box 113)
    - Sanford, Terry [President of Duke University], 1995 (Box 113)
    - Sanford, Terry [President of Duke University], 1996 (Box 113)
    - Sanford, Terry [President of Duke University], 1997 (Box 113)
    - Sanford, Terry [President of Duke University], post-1998 (Box 113)
    - Sanford, Terry [President of Duke University - Bio and CVs] (Box 113)
    - Sanford, Terry [President of Duke University - Death and Funeral], d. 4/48/1998 (Box 113)
    - Semans, James Hustead [Urology; Trustee Mary Duke Biddle Foundation; Husband of Mary D.B.T. Semans] (Box 113)
    - Schewel, Steve [Alumnus] (Box 113)
    - Slaughter, Frank G. [Alumnus; M.D.; Author] (Box 113)
    - Smeal, Eleanor [Alumna] (Box 113)
    - Sosnik, Doug [Alumnus; Sr. Advisor to Pres. Bill Clinton] (Box 113)
    - Stedman, W. David [Alumnus; Dist. Alumni Award 1989] (Box 113)
    - Styron, William [Alumnus; Author], 1 of 2 (Box 113)
    - Styron, William [Alumnus; Author], 2 of 2 (Box 113)
    - Starr, Kenneth [Alumnus, Law 1973] (Box 113)
    - Tally, Joe [Alumnus; Mayor of Fayetteville, N.C. (1949-1953); Pres., Kiwanis International] (Box 113)
    - Thomas, R. David [Founder of Wendy's restaurants; Founding donor of the R. David Thomas Center for Executive Education at Fuqua Business] (Box 113)
    - Townes, Charles H. [Alumnus; Nobel Prize for physics (1964); Advisor, Apollo space missions (1960s)] (Box 113)
    - Tuttle, Lee F. [Alumnus; Football); Secretary, World Methodist Council] (Box 113)
    - Tyler (Modarressi), Anne [Alumna; Author; Pulitzer Prize for Breathing Lessons] (Box 113)
    - Vincent, James [Alumnus; CEO, Biogen; Univ. Trustee] (Box 113)
    - Wall, Art, Jr. [Alumnus; 1959 Masters Champion (golf); Member Duke Sports Hall of Fame], d. 10/31/2001 (Box 113)
    - Wagoner, Richard, Jr. [Alumnus; Basketball (1970s); CEO General Motors] (Box 113)
    - Waller, Robert [Alumnus (T 1958); CEO, Mayo Clinic] (Box 113)
    - Warner, Frank [Alumnus (T 1925); Collector and singer of traditional American folk music] (Box 113)
    - Weaver, L. Stacy [Alumnus; Pres., Methodist College (Fayetteville, N.C.)] (Box 113)
    - Westcott, Jacqueline Renee [Alumna; Commissioner of social services] (Box 113)
    - Westmoreland, Timothy [Alumnus (T 1976); Center for Medicaid and State Operations] (Box 113)
    - Wise, Bob [Alumnus; Gov., West Virginia] (Box 113)
    - Woodruff, Judy [Alumna; Anchor CNN] (Box 113)
    - Woodwell, George [Alumnus; Woods Hole Research Center] (Box 113)
    - Wright, Maurice [Alumnus (1972 A.B. Music. Magna cum laude; musician and composer] (Box 113)
    - Zimmerman, Maj. Gen. Matthew [Alumnus (Divinity 1965); First Black graduate from Duke Divinity School; Veterans' Affairs National Chaplain Center] (Box 113)
    - Keohane, Nannerl O. [8th President of Duke University - Biographical Sketch] (Box 114)
    - Keohane, Nannerl O. [8th President of Duke University - Education File] (Box 114)
    - Keohane, Nannerl O. [8th President of Duke University - Presidential Announcement] (Box 114)
    - Keohane, Nannerl O. [8th President of Duke University - Speeches] (Box 114)
    - Keohane, Nannerl O. [8th President of Duke University], 1985-1992 (Box 114)
    - Keohane, Nannerl O. [8th President of Duke University], 1993 (Box 114)
    - Keohane, Nannerl O. [8th President of Duke University], 1994 (Box 114)
    - Keohane, Nannerl O. [8th President of Duke University], 1995 (Box 114)
    - Keohane, Nannerl O. [8th President of Duke University], 1996 (Box 114)
    - Keohane, Nannerl O. [8th President of Duke University], 1997 (Box 114)
    - Keohane, Nannerl O. [8th President of Duke University], 1998 (Box 114)
    - Keohane, Nannerl O. [8th President of Duke University], 1999 (Box 114)
    - Keohane, Nannerl O. [8th President of Duke University], 2000- (Box 114)
  - Trustees (Box 114)
    - Trustees (Box 115)
    - Duke University Trustees (Box 115)
    - Trustees, General (Box 115)
    - Trustees, General, 1979 (Box 115)
    - Trustees, General, 1987 (Box 115)
    - Trustees, General, 1988 (Box 115)
    - Trustees, General, 1989 (Box 115)
    - Trustees, General, 1990 (Box 115)
    - Trustees, General, 1991 (Box 115)
    - Trustees, General, 1998 (Box 115)
    - Trustees, General, 2001 (Box 115)
    - Trustees, General, 2002 (Box 115)
    - Board of Trustees Meetings (Box 115)
    - Adams, Rex D., Trustee 1995-2001 (Box 115)
    - Alderman, S. S., retired June 6, 1959 (Box 115)
    - Aldridge, Thomas A. (Box 115)
    - Allen, George G. (Box 115)
    - Allen, George V. (Box 115)
    - Alston, Wilton D. (Box 115)
    - Anderson, Albert (Box 115)
    - Barnhardt, J. H. (Box 115)
    - Barnes, Samuel Henry, Trustee 1989- (Box 115)
    - Baugh, Philip Jackson "Jack", Trustee 1988- (Box 115)
    - Bazinsky, Jordan (Box 115)
    - Bell, James Ardrey (Box 115)
    - Bell, W. B. (Box 115)
    - Benenson, Edward H. (Box 115)
    - Blue, Daniel T., Jr., Trustee 1995-1999 (Box 115)
    - Bostock, Roy J. (Box 115)
    - Boulware, C. E. (Box 115)
    - Bowles, Charles Phillips (Box 115)
    - Bowling, E. S. (Box 115)
    - Bradshaw, Robert, deceased 7-29-67 (Box 115)
    - Brian, Mrs. Earl W. (Box 115)
    - Briggs, Arnold (Box 115)
    - Brim, Kenneth (Box 115)
    - Brown, Werner C. (Box 115)
    - Bruton, John F. (Box 115)
    - Cannon, Charles Albert (Box 115)
    - Cannon, William R. (Box 115)
    - Chambers, Julius (Box 115)
    - Cherry, R. G. (Box 115)
    - Clegg, W. L. (Box 115)
    - Cocke, Norman A. (Box 115)
    - Cook, Samuel DuBois, Trustee 1981-1993 (Box 115)
    - Cook, Samuel DuBois, 1994- (Box 115)
    - Cooke, Wilhelmina R. (Box 115)
    - Council, C. T. (Box 115)
    - Cox, J. Elwood (Box 115)
    - Cuninggim, Merrimon (Box 115)
    - Dale, Kathleen Watkins (Box 116)
    - Davis, Walter R. (Box 116)
    - Davis, Graham (Box 116)
    - Deane, Disque D., Trustee 1983-1989 (Box 116)
    - Dodds, Sarah Caroline, Trustee 1995-1998 (Box 116)
    - Donnell, Edward S. (Box 116)
    - Doss, Henry Clay (Box 116)
    - Drill, Isobel Craven Martin Lewis (Box 116)
    - Duke, Mrs. J. B. [Endowment Trustee] (Box 116)
    - Duke, Tony (Box 116)
    - Dula, C. C. (Box 116)
    - Durham, Christine M. (Box 116)
    - Edgerton, Norman Edward (Box 116)
    - Elias, D. S. (Box 116)
    - Elrod, Sara R. (Box 116)
    - Esrey, Julie Campbell (Box 116)
    - Edwards, Alonzo (Box 116)
    - Farquhar, Michele (Box 116)
    - Few, Ben F. (Box 116)
    - Finch, Thomas A. (Box 116)
    - Flowers, W. W. (Box 116)
    - Frizzelle, J. P., Trustee 1937-58 (Box 116)
    - Fuqua, John Brooks (Box 116)
    - Garrett, Nathan T., Trustee July 1977 (Box 116)
    - Gates, Melinda French (Box 116)
    - Gavin, James R. III (Box 116)
    - Grant, Thomas M., Deceased 12-31-1952 (Box 116)
    - Griffith, Kathleen (Box 116)
    - Grune, George V., Trustee 1987 (Box 116)
    - Hanes, P. Frank (Box 116)
    - Hanks, Nancy (Box 116)
    - Hardin, Paul III [includes family photos] (Box 116)
    - Hardin, Paul III, Trustee 1995-2001 (Box 116)
    - Harper, Robert T., Trustee 1996-1998 (Box 116)
    - Harris, R. Ross, Chairman 1988 (Box 116)
    - Harriss, J. Welch (Box 116)
    - Heidrick, Robert L., Trustee 1989- (Box 116)
    - Herbert, George Richard, Trustee 1985-1991 (Box 116)
    - Hillman, Jennifer [Student Trustee] (Box 116)
    - Hoadley, Walter E. (Box 116)
    - Hobbs, William J. (Box 116)
    - Holloway, Benjamin Duke (Box 116)
    - Horne, Josh L., deceased 3/1974 (Box 116)
    - Houck, Calvin Bryan (Box 116)
    - Howard, Steven (Box 116)
    - Hudson, Jerry Fitzgerald S. (Box 116)
    - Hull, Alma [Alumnae President 1949] (Box 116)
    - Hunt, Alfred M. (Box 116)
    - Hurley, J. B. (Box 116)
    - Inman, Walker P. [Duke Endowment Trustee, Doris Duke's 1/2 Brother], d. 1954 (Box 116)
    - Ivey, George M., d. 5/1968 (Box 116)
    - Jeffries, Shaver Dakal, Trustee 1996-1999 (Box 116)
    - Jenkins, Kimberly (Box 116)
    - Johnson, F. Ross, Trustee 1987- (Box 116)
    - Johnson, Jeff D., d. 6/1960 (Box 116)
    - Jones, Edwin L., Jr. (Box 116)
    - Jones, E. L., Sr. (Box 116)
    - Jordan, B. Everett [University Trustee, Alumnus], d. 3/1974 (Box 116)
    - Judd, Walter H. [Commencement Speaker], 1949 (Box 116)
    - Kearns, Amos Ragan, d. 7/1979 (Box 116)
    - King, Susan, Trustee 1987 (Box 116)
    - Kirby, Wallace (Box 116)
    - Kirk, John Franklin [University Trustee, Alumnus] (Box 116)
    - Kirkland, Rebecca Trent, Trustee 1995-2001 (Box 116)
    - Kiser, J. J., Trustee to 2001 (Box 116)
    - Knowles, John Hilton, d. 3/1978 (Box 116)
    - Kohn, Carol L. A. (Box 116)
    - Koskinen, John A., Trustee 1988- (Box 116)
    - Kurzweil, Jeffrey [Student Trustee] (Box 116)
    - Lam, Christopher, Trustee thru 2001 (Box 116)
    - Lambeth, Charles Franklin (Box 116)
    - Lane, William A., Jr. "Bill" (Box 116)
    - Lee, W. S. [Duke Endowment Trustee ], d. 3/24/1934 (Box 116)
    - Long, James Anderson [University Trustee, Alumnus] (Box 116)
    - Mack, John J. (Box 117)
    - Mario, Ernest (Box 117)
    - Marr, Thomas Franklin (Box 117)
    - Marshall, E. C. [Duke Endowment Trustee] (Box 117)
    - Mayer, Robert Andrews, d. 8/1/1969 (Box 117)
    - McGhee, George C. (Box 117)
    - McMahon, Alex (Box 117)
    - Miller, Ben N. (Box 117)
    - Minnick, Carlton, P., Trustee 1989- (Box 117)
    - Mullen, Kevin E., Trustee 1994-1997 (Box 117)
    - Muller, William H., Jr. (Box 117)
    - Murphy, Charles S. (Box 117)
    - Nahmias, David, Trustee 1988- (Box 117)
    - Nasher, Raymond (Box 117)
    - Nease, Edgar Harrison, Sr. (Box 117)
    - Nelson, Margaret, Trustee 1989 (Box 117)
    - Nesbit, Takcus (Box 117)
    - Newsome, Clarence (Box 117)
    - Newsom, M. E. (Box 117)
    - Nichols, Peter (Box 117)
    - November, Martin, Trustee 1988- (Box 117)
    - Odell, W. R. (Box 117)
    - Page, Henry Allison (Box 117)
    - Parker, W. C. [Duke Endowment Trustee] (Box 117)
    - Parrish, Alexander W. (Box 117)
    - Patterson, Eugene C., Trustee 1988- (Box 117)
    - Peacock, Dred (Box 117)
    - Peele, W. W. (Box 117)
    - Perkins, Thomas Lee [Duke Endowment Trustee and Chairman], d. 6/21/1973 (Box 117)
    - Perkins, William Robinson [Duke Endowment Trustee and Vice Chairman], d. 6/15/1945 (Box 117)
    - Pickens, Marshall I. [Duke Endowment Trustee and Chairman] (Box 117)
    - Pierce, F. Grainger, d. 10/30/1958 (Box 117)
    - Pinnix, Robert H. (Box 117)
    - Pitts, William R., d. 4/1960 (Box 117)
    - Porter, Hubbard Braxton (Box 117)
    - Postma, Herman, Trustee 1987-1993 (Box 117)
    - Pratt, Edmund T., Jr. (Box 117)
    - Proctor, C. K., Trustee July 1977 (Box 117)